我的小不点儿
Who the winny-binny boy?
你是个小小的小不点儿
You the winny-winny-binny-binny boy!
不要哭啊
Don't cry.
不要哭嘛
他为什么还在哭？
Why is he still crying?
不要担心，没什么东西不能用“快乐钥匙”搞定的
Don't worry. It's nothing that can't be solved by " happy keys. "
当有人在我面前晃动有缺口的金属时我就会感觉很好
I feel better when someone shakes jagged metal in my face.
好了，这里
All right, here.
我来抱他一下
Let me hold him for a sec.
来，爸爸抱
Here we go.
不哭了
There we are.
或许是因为我
Maybe it's me.
别傻了，班爱你 他只是有点像怪癖裤子先生（卡通形象经常说“别碰我”）
Don't be silly. Ben loves you. He's just being Mr. Cranky Pants.
我曾跟一个怪癖裤子小姐约会过
You know,I once dated a Miss Cranky Pants.
好女孩，有点情绪化就是了
Lovely girl. IKind of moody.
好了，好多了
There we go,all better.
这才是小乖乖
There's my little boy.
我可以试一件事吗？
Can I see something?
酷哎
Cool!
他恨我，我的┳雍尬
He hates me. My nephew hates me!
-我没了工作而且他恨我 -别这样说嘛
-l' m unemployed and he hates me.-Don't do this.
你只有没工作而已
You' re just unemployed.
要是我自己孩子恨我 怎么办啊？
What if my own baby hates me? What do I do then?
莫妮卡，你住口好不好？ 你疯了是不是啊？
Monica,stop! This is nuts.
你知道你还要多久 才会遇到这个问题呢？
Do you know how long it'll be before you have to deal with this?
我是说你现在连男朋友都没有
You don't even have a boyfriend yet.
乔伊，她看起来不胖
Joey,she does not look fat.
六人行 第2季 第06集 宝宝落在巴士上了
The One With the Baby on the Bus
拿去
Here you go.
咕，咕，咕！
Goo,goo,goo!
真好笑，那个借我一下
That is so funny! Let me see that a sec.
你还好吧，罗斯？
You okay?
不知道
I don't know.
馅饼里有什么呀？
What's in this pie?
不知道，奶油，鸡蛋，面粉 莱姆，奇异果跟…
I don't know. Butter and eggs and flour and lime and kiwi
奇异果？奇异果？
Kiwi? Kiwi?!
你说这个是奇莱馅饼
You said it was a key lime pie.
不是，我是说奇异果莱姆 所以才会那么特别
No,I didn't. I said kiwi lime. That's what makes it so special.
所以我才会死
That's what's gonna kill me.
我对奇异果过敏
I'm allergic to kiwi.
你才不会呢 你会过敏的是龙虾，花生跟…
No,you're not. You're allergic to lobster and peanuts and
天啊
Oh,my God!
越来越严重了
It's definitely getting worse.
你的舌头肿了吗？
Is your tongue swelling up?
要不然就是我的嘴小了
Either that or my mouth is getting smaller!
穿外套，我们现在就到医院去
Get your coat. We're going to the hospital.
他不会怎么样吧？ 不会，只是得打一针
-Will he be okay? -He's gotta get a shot.
事实上我觉得好多了
You know,actually,it's getting better. It is.
没错，别去了 谁要玩拼字游戏啊？
Let's not go. Anyone up for Scrabble?
去穿外套
Jacket,now!
但是班怎么办呢？ 我们不能带个宝宝去医院啊
What about Ben? We can't bring a baby to the hospital.
交给我们吧
We'll watch him.
恕难从命
I don't think so.
干嘛？我有七个天主教姐妹 我照顾过上百个小孩
I have seven Catholic sisters. I've taken care of hundreds of kids.
别这样 我们想帮忙，对不对？
Come on,we want to do it. Don't we?
拜托，我本来想去打篮球的…
I was gonna play basketball...
…不过球被丢出窗外去了
... but I guess that's out the window.
好，如果你要带他去散步 记得要帮他戴帽子，好吗？
If you take him out for a walk,remember to bring his hat.
冰箱里还有一些牛奶 尿布在袋子里
There's milk in the refrigerator and diapers in the bag.
帽子，牛奶…
Hat,milk....
懂了
Got it!
包在我身上啊
Consider it done!
你听得懂吗？
You understood?
懂啊，我沙叔叔就有大舌头
My uncle Sal has a really big tongue.
是老婆很漂亮的那个？
Is he the one with the beautiful wife?
中央公园
瑞秋，要不要听听 我今天下午要唱的新歌呢？
You want to hear the song I'm singing this afternoon?
今天早上洗澡的时候写的
I wrote it this morning in the shower.
我一边洗澡一边在写歌
I'm in the shower And I'm writing a song
听过的话请阻止我
Stop me if you've heard it
我全身泡沫，头发湿搭搭
My skin is soapy and my hair is wet
香皂倒过来是皂香
And Tegrin spelled backward is nirget
瑞秋，亲爱的 麻烦你过来一下好吗？
Rachel,sweetheart,could I see you for a minute?
什么事啊？
What's up?
告诉你…
FYI:
我决定以后周日的下午 要付钱请一位职业歌手来演出
I've decided to pay a professional musician to play here on Sundays.
她叫什么芬的，很出色的
Her name is Stephanie something. She's supposed to be very good.
但菲比怎么办？
But what about Phoebe?
瑞秋，你的朋友不只是差而已
It's not that your friend is bad.
她实在是差到…
It's that she's so bad...
差到让我想把手指头 伸进我的眼睛里
...she makes me want to put my finger through my eye into my brain...
然后把脑袋搅成浆糊
...and swirl it around.
那好，你不是她的歌迷
Okay,so you're not a fan.
可是你不能这样对她嘛
But,I mean,come on. You cannot do this to her.
你叫我出面？
I have to do this to her?
涂皂，冲水，再一次…
Lather,rinse,repeat
And lather,rinse,repeat
涂皂，冲水，再一次…
视需要而定
As needed
我觉得我们东西没有带够
We didn't bring enough stuff.
你有没有记得 把宝宝的止痛药带出来？
Did you forget to pack the baby's anvil?
我告诉你，这绝对值得
I'm telling you,it'll be worth it.
大家都知道女人最爱宝宝了
It's a known fact that women love babies.
女人爱喜欢宝宝的男人 这是感性的问题，懂了吗？
Women love guys who love babies. It's the sensitive thing.
把他对准那边那些宝贝 说不定待会儿有一个会过来
Aim him at that pack of babes. Maybe one of them will break away.
不…等一下 算了，正左方
Wait,forget them. We got one. Hard left.
来，宝宝给我 不要，我要抱
-Give me the baby. -No,I got him.
快，我说真的
Come on,seriously.
你真的要他吗？
Oh,seriously,you want him?
这个小可爱是谁啊？
Who is this little cutie-pie?
不要怪我不懂得谦虚，但…
Well,don't think me immodest,but...
…我
... me.
要不要嗅嗅他？
Want to smell him?
我想你指的是宝宝吧？
I assume we're talking about the baby?
是呀，他的宝宝味好香 嗅嗅他的头
He's got that great baby smell. Get a whiff of his head.
我想我的子宫刚刚顿了一下
My uterus just skipped a beat.
你看吧
What'd I tell you?
我觉得你们这样做很棒
It's great you're doing this.
我们都是很棒的男人
Well,we are great guys.
我弟弟跟他的男友 试了三年都领养不到孩子
My brother and his boyfriend have been trying to adopt.
你们是找哪一家办的？
What agency did you two go through?
这是我的表演
But this is my gig.
这是我的地盘
This is where I play.
我的名字用粉笔写在外面
My name is written out there in chalk.
你不能把粉笔擦掉的
You know,you can't just erase chalk.
对不起，我很遗撼
Honey,I'm sorry.
而且他居然还要付这个女人钱
And he's going to be paying this woman?
那他干脆给她一个宝座 一顶皇冠
Why doesn't he just give her a throne and a crown?
还有一根上面有球的权杖
And,like,a gold stick with a ball on top?
特瑞是混蛋，所以我们才会 常说“特瑞是混蛋”
Terry is a jerk! That's why we always say,"Terry's a jerk!"
不然我们干嘛那么说
That's where that came from.
你说不定已经尽力了
You probably did everything you could.
好吧，这样让我看看 还有没有别的办法
You know what? Let me just see what else I could do.
你何不让她接在那个史黛芬的后面唱啊？
Just let her go on after Stephanie whatever her name is.
你又不在这里，又不付她钱
You won't be here. You don't pay her.
我不知道
I don't know.
我帮你洗卡布奇诺机好吗
I'll clean the cappuccino machine!
你没洗过卡布奇诺机吗？
You don't clean the cappuccino machine?
我当然洗了
Of course I clean it.
我是说我会清洗
I mean,I will clean it.
我会清的
好…
All right,fine,fine,fine!
成了 真的？
-Done. -Really?
对呀，看谁出马嘛
Who's working for you,babe?
天啊，好兴奋哦 我会收到多少钱啊？
Oh,my God! This is so exciting! How much am I gonna get?
什么？
What?
你说他要付钱给演出的人
He's paying the people who were playing.
我是说他要付另外那个女人钱 因为她是职业歌手
I meant,he's paying that other woman because she's a professional.
我可不想当那个 唯一没有收到钱的人
I'm not gonna be the only one who's not getting paid.
对不起，不
I'm sorry,no!
不，我可不是什么二流的… 慈善乐团
No,I'm not some sloppy second,you know,charity band.
这个城市里面有上千个地方…
There are thousands of places in this city...
…愿意付钱听我来演唱
...where people would pay to hear me play.
我为自己而演唱
When I play,I play for me
我不需要你的施舍
I don't need your charity
谢谢
Thank you!
你说什么都别想叫我打针 我是说，或许他们可以把…
I'm not getting a shot. Maybe they can take the needle...
…药水射进我的嘴里 就像水枪那样
...and squirt it into my mouth. Like a squirt gun.
看看医生怎么说吧
See what the doctor says.
他们已经做了些事情了，现在都是九十年代了
They've got to do something.These are the ' 90s.
你们好，我是卡林医生
Hello there. I'm Dr. Carlin.
好像有人有一点点过敏的反应
I see someone's having a little allergic reaction.
对，医生 我可以单独跟你谈谈吗？
Doctor,can I see you for just a moment?
我哥哥有一点点害怕打针
My brother has a slight phobia about needles.
你有没有告诉他 我那个水枪的主意？
Did you tell him about my squirt gun idea?
我的博士哥哥想知道…
My brother,the Ph.D.,would like to know...
这个药有没有可能用口服的？
...if there's any way to treat this orally?
在这种情况之下，打针是 避免不了的，而且要马上打针
Under these circumstances,it has to be an injection,and it has to be now.
怎么样？
So?
好吧，坐下来 医生说这一针非打不可
Go and have a seat. The doctor says it's got to be a needle.
所以你一定要勇敢起来 为我这么做，好不好？
You're just going to have to be brave. Can you do that for me?
你做得非常好
Oh,boy! You are doing so good.
要不要握紧我的手啊？
You want to squeeze my hand?
罗斯，不要握得那么紧
Ross,don't squeeze it so hard.
真的，不要握那么紧
Honey,really. Don't squeeze it so hard!
罗斯，放开我的手
Let go of my hand!
还真是个好计划 下一回想泡妞…
Good plan. Next time we want to pick up women...
…我们干脆直接去公园 亲热算了
...we should go to the park and make out.
计程车…
Taxi! Taxi!
你看那妞儿
Look at that talent.
只是在练习，你很行
Just practicing. You're good.
继续开吧
Carry on.
等等，等等我们
Wait,wait,wait!
他好可爱哦
Hey,you. He's just adorable.
告诉他，好不好？ 他觉得他脸色太红润了
Can you tell him that? Because he thinks he looks too pink.
你们今天出来做什么？ 我们没有
-What are you guys out doing today? -We're not out.
我们只是帮我们的 异性恋朋友…
We're two heterosexual guys hanging with the son...
…带孩子的异性恋男人 做一般男人应该做的事情
...of our other heterosexual friend,doing the usual straight-guy stuff.
讲完了？
You done?
我们到了
There's our stop.
少来了，我们才到了
Get out of here! This is our stop.
你们也住在这附近啊？
You guys live around here too?
我们住在那个人行道旁边
We live in the building by the sidewalk.
你们知道吗？
You know it?
对了，既然大家是邻居嘛 我们聚一聚喝点东西，如何？
Since we're neighbors,what do you say we get together for a drink?
我们去马可咖啡厅，好吗？
So you want to go to Markel's?
好啊，他们很喜欢我们
Sure,they love us over there.
你们的宝宝呢？
Where's your baby?
班…
Ben! Ben!
或许他会听到并且自己拉铃（下车）
That's good. Maybe he'll hear you and pull the cord!
停车
Stop the bus!
你肯定没有捏断？我真的很痛
Are you sure he didn't break it? It hurts.
没有，只是有一块瘀青
No,it's just a good bone bruise.
还有这是你戒指压出来的痕迹
And right here is the puncture wound from your ring.
对不起，我真的很抱歉 没关系
-I'm really sorry. -It's okay.
抱歉…
Sorry.
抱歉…我说清楚了
Sorry! I got my S's back!
那我们待会儿再庆祝
Which we can celebrate later.
庆祝…
Celebrate. Celebrate....
他是个双双双
He was a double,double
双关节男孩
Double-jointed boy
你就是那个专业的吉他手吗？
So are you the professional guitar player?
对，我叫史黛芬
Yeah,I'm Stephanie.
对，上面本来有我名字的 现在只剩红萝N糕了
Right. My name was on there,but now it just says carrot cake.
你会弹几个和弦？
So how many chords do you know?
全都会啊 是吗？那你会D调
-All of them. -So you know D?
那你会A小调吗？
Do you know A-minor?
你会从D和弦转到A小调吗？
Do you know how to go from D to A-minor?
那你的吉他有背带吗？
So does your guitar have a strap?
我的有
Mine does.
史黛芬和弦都会
Stephanie knows all the chords
快接…
Come on! Pick up,pick up!
运输中心吗？
Transit Authority?
我在帮一本书做调查
I'm doing research for a book.
如果有人把婴儿留在城市公交车上 那该怎么办呢？
I was wondering what somebody might do if they left a baby on a city bus.
是，我知道 只有笨蛋才会这么做
Yes,I realize that would be a stupid character.
我们今天在公车上 掉了汽车安全座椅
Here's the deal: We lost a car seat on a bus.
白塑胶材质 有把手，可以用在推车上面
It's white plastic and it fits onto a stroller.
里面还有一个婴儿
And there was a baby in it.
他要跟你讲
He wants to talk to you.
各位 我们以最热烈的掌声欢迎…
Everybody,let's give a warm Central Perk welcome to
特瑞是个混蛋 他不让我工作
Terry's a jerk And he won't let me work
我恨中央咖啡厅
And I hate Central Perk
欢迎史黛芬
To Stephanie Schiffer!
首先我想唱一首 我为我的初恋情人写的歌
I'd like to start with a song I wrote for the first man I ever loved.
柴克力…
Zachary
被邀来咬我
Are all invited to bite me
我们打过电话来公车上的婴儿 怎么样了？到了没有…
We're the guys that called about the baby! Is he here?!
到了
He's here.
你们之中有一个是父亲吧
I assume one of you is the father.
是我 是我
-That's me. -I'm him.
事实上呢，我们两个都是父亲
Actually,we're both the father.
宝贝…
Oh,Ben! Hey,buddy.
你知道哪个是班吗？
Please tell me you know which one is our baby.
那个T恤上有鸭子 这个有小丑
That one has ducks on his T-shirt and this one has clowns.
班绝对是穿着鸭子T恤的
And Ben was definitely wearing ducks.
或小丑
Or clowns.
等一下，那个绝对是班 记得他嘴边那颗可爱的小痣
That one's Ben! Remember he had that cute little mole by his mouth!
班，记得我们吗？
Hey,Ben! Remember us?
天啊，痣掉了
Okay,the mole came off.
我们该怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
丢铜板决定，鸭或小丑
We'll flip for it. Ducks or clowns.
要丢铜板决定 你有更好的主意吗？
-Flip for the baby? -You got a better idea?
好吧，在空中叫
All right,call it in the air.
头
Heads.
就是头
Heads,it is.
我们得先决定头是哪一个
We have to assign heads to something!
好的！
Right!
鸭子是头，因为鸭子有头
Ducks is heads because ducks have heads.
帮你庆祝生日的小丑没有头 不会吓坏你吗？
What kind of scary-ass clowns came to your birthday?
叫我清晨天使
Just call me angel Of the morning,angel
在离开我之前 轻触我的脸颊
Just touch my cheek Before you leave me,baby
叫我清晨天使
Just call me angel Of the morning,angel
然后转身离去
Then slowly turn away
我不会求你留下来
I won't beg you to stay
陪我
With me
来，我想你可能会冷
Here. I thought you might be cold.
谢谢
Thank you.
看看你，干得不错嘛
Look at you! You did pretty well.
这里一共是八块又二十七分
$8. 27.
其实没那么多啦 头两块是我放的
But not really,because I put in the first two.
只是让钱滚滚来 还有让自己舒服一点
Just to get the ball rolling and to make myself feel better.
结果呢？
Do you?
为了钱演奏这码子事 对我非常的不好
You know,this whole playing for money thing is so not good for me.
我不知道 当我唱到“自自自自杀”…
I don't know,when l sang "Su-su-suicide"...
…我得到一块七十五分钱
... I got,like,$ 1. 75.
可是“臭臭猫”呢？
But then "Smelly Cat"?
二十五分钱跟一个保险套
I got 25 cents and a condom.
所以现在我为“臭臭猫” 感到很难过
So,you know,now I just feel really bad for "Smelly Cat."
我不认为 大家都会懂“臭臭猫”啊
Honey,I don't think everybody gets "Smelly Cat."
我是说 如果你只要养过健康的猫的话
I mean,if all you've ever actually had are healthy pets,then whoosh!
可是根本就不是那个嘛
But it's not even that,you know?
本来我唱歌只是因为我很高兴
I used to do my songs because it made me happy.
可是现在却变成全都是为了钱
Now it's just all about the money,you know?
菲比，大家都很想你
Well,people missed you in there.
事实上 还有人指名要听“臭臭猫”呢
In fact,there was actually a request for "Smelly Cat."
真的啊？是谁呢？
Really? From who?
我啊，就是我
Well,me.
我知道那不是赚大钱的歌 但我最喜欢的就是那首
And I know it's not your big money song,but it's my favorite.
我是不是 不小心丢了一个保险套到你的盒子里啊？
Did I accidentally drop a condom in your case?
情况紧急嘛
It's kind of an emergency.
拿去吧 谢了
-Here you go. -Thanks a lot.
克丽丝，拿到了
Hey,Christine! I got it!
我只是想要谢谢你今天的帮忙
I want to thank you for being there for me.
对不起，我差点捏断你的手
And I'm sorry I almost broke your hand.
没关系，抱歉你中了我的毒
That's okay. I'm sorry I poisoned you.
你还记得 我用铅笔戳你的手那回吗？
Remember the time I jammed that pencil into your hand?
记得吗？ 你以为这是什么？雀斑啊
Remember it? What do you think this is,a freckle?
等等，那我用薇恩的南瓜 打你脸那一次呢？
What about the time I hit you in the face with Sylvian's pumpkin?
天啊，记得我把扫把 插进你脚踏车轮里…
Remember when I stuck that broom in your spokes...
结果你翻车头撞到路边那次吗
...and you hit your head on the curb?
不，但是我记得是别人告诉我那件事
But I remember people telling me about it.
我希望班有个小妹妹
I hope Ben has a little sister.
希望她能够好好的整整他
And I hope she can kick his ass.
我去拿一个新的创可贴
I'm gonna get a new Band-Aid.
我切下你马里布肯娃娃的腿那次呢？
How about the time I cut the legs off your Malibu Ken?
是你干的啊？
That was you?
对，它的腿发炎了 不切的话它会死
They were infected. He wouldn't have made it.
我的小┳
My little nephew.
过来，小东西
Come here,little one!
我的小宝贝班班
There's my little baby,Ben!
他居然没有哭
Hey,he's not crying!
他没哭呀
还有馅饼
There's still pie!
我在，我在
I'm here. I'm here.
我的小宝贝好吗？
How's my little boy?
要爸爸帮你换尿布，对不对？ 我知道…
You want Daddy to change your diaper? I know,I know.
你今天跟乔伊叔叔 还有钱德叔叔玩得开心吗？
Did you have fun with Uncle Joey and Uncle Chandler today?
开心，他今天坐公车了
He rode the bus today.
好耶，大男生坐公车喔
Big boy riding the bus
我有个问题耶
Hey,I have a question.
他的小屁股上为什么会有 “失物招领”这些字？
How come it says,"Property of Human Services"?
你一定会觉得很精采的
You are gonna love this.
帮我抱一下班，好吗？
Can you hold Ben for a sec?
过来…
Come here. Come here.
别过来，我有奇异果 跑呀，乔伊
Stay back! I've got kiwi! Run,Joey,run!
臭臭猫…
Smelly cat,smelly cat
他们都喂你吃些什么啊？
What are they feeding you?
不对…对不起
No,no. I'm sorry,it's:
臭臭猫…
Smelly cat,smelly cat
好一点了
Better!
好多了
Much better. Good.
你知道吗？不要难过 这首歌本来就很难
Don't feel bad,because it's a hard song.
要不要再试一次？ 好，从头
-You want to try it again? -From the top?
这次没有头，好吗？
There is no "top," all right?
那是“臭臭猫”的美妙之处
That's the beauty of "Smelly Cat."
你跟着我唱好了 好
Why don't you just follow me.
臭臭猫…
Smelly cat,smelly cat
他们喂你什么？
What are they feeding you?
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
不是你的错
It's not your fault
太过了。-对不起
That's too much. Sorry.